http://www.linkmicrotek.com/privacy-policy

Call: +44 (0)1256 355771Email: sales@linkmicrotek.com
Call usEmail us
HomeAboutLink Microtek NewsLink Microtek Blog Archive NewsCompany PoliciesPrincipalsCase StudiesProductsDesignEMF SafetyIR CommsTest & MeasurementComponentsAmplifiers/Electron DevicesSatcomFeaturedRotary JointsNardalert S3Sunsight AAT-30 Antenna Alignment ToolRadMan 2LT & XT EMF Personal MonitorProduct SearchDesignComponentsRotary JointsSub-systemsProduct SearchEMF SafetyOur Products Personal MonitorsSurvey EquipmentArea Monitors & SoftwareProduct SupportCalibration & MaintenanceMeasurement ServicesApplication NotesTraining ServicesFAQsEMF NewsEMF BlogTrainingEMF Safety Course - RegistrationEMF Safety Tutorial - RegistrationOptical CommsAbout AzdecSystem OverviewApplicationsNavalAir Traffic ControlOther ApplicationsFAQsData SheetsLatest NewsTest & MeasurementNarda Test SolutionsSAFAWT GlobalSunsightContactCareers
HomePrivacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Last Updated on 15th May 2018. This Privacy Policy is effective immediately for Users after that date.
Link Microtek Ltd qualifies as a Data Controller under the Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of The European Parliament and of The Council of 27 April 2016 (General Data Protection Regulation (the “GDPR”)). As such, we aim to comply with all legal obligations which the GDPR implies on Data Controllers.
Link Microtek Ltd respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it through our compliance with this Privacy Policy.
1. Definitions
In this Policy the following terms have these meanings:
“Cookie” means a small text file placed on your computer or device by our website when you visit our website;
“Our website” means this website, www.linkmicrotek.com;
“Personal data” means data that we process which is any information that can be personally attributable to an individual such as a name, email address or telephone number;
“We/Us/Our” means Link Microtek Ltd, a limited company Registered in England under Company Number 03046907, whose registered address is High Point, Church Street, Basingstoke, Hampshire, RG21 7QN.
2. About this policy
This policy describes:
The types of information that we may collect from you when you access or use our website – www.linkmicrotek.com; or interact with us; and
Our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting and disclosing that information.
This policy applies only to information we collect through our services and in the electronic communications sent through or in connection with our services.
Our Data Protection Officer
The Data Protection Officer at Link Microtek Ltd is Michelle Millet.
3. What data do we collect?
Some data will be collected automatically by our website and other data will only be collected if you voluntarily submit it.
Automatically collected data, which includes data collected through Google Analytics will be non-personally identifiable data.
Data collected that you have voluntarily submitted may be personally identifiable data.
Depending upon your use of our website, we may collect some or all of the following data:
1. Name2. Business/company name3. Email addresses4. Telephone number5. Address details6. Enquiry message/detail7. Browsing statistics and behaviour via Google Analytics (automatically collected)
4. How we use the information we collect
We use the information that we collect from you in a variety of ways.
This includes:
Operations
We use the information to provide the services and information that you request and to respond to enquiries, requests and questions.
Cookies and tracking technologies
We use collected information through cookies and similar technologies to:
Monitor site usage statistics such as total number of visitors and pages viewed;
Track your behaviour after receiving an email newsletter or digital marketing material from Link Microtek Ltd including open rate and links clicked;
Cookies on our website
_gat, _ga, _gid
Google Analytics: We use Google Analytics to monitor traffic levels, search queries and visits to this website.
cookieconsent_dismissed
Cookie Consent: The cookie tool on this website remembers your privacy settings for the next time you visit the website.
You can obtain more information about cookies by visiting http://www.allaboutcookies.org
Google Analytics
We use Google Analytics to measure and evaluate access to and traffic on our website, and to create user navigation and behaviour reports for our website administrators and marketing team.
Data collected from Google Analytics is not attributable to an individual.
5. Storing and sharing your data
Do we keep your data?
We keep your data:
-  for as long as we need to in order to use it as described above in section 4;and/or,-  for as long as we have your permission to keep it, such as using it to send you our newsletter or other marketing materials;and/or,-  if you are an active client.
Where do we keep your data?
Personally identifiable data that you submit through our website will not be stored or transferred outside of the European Economic Area (“the EEA”) (The EEA consists of all EU member states, plus Norway, Iceland and Liechtenstein).
Do We Share Your Data?
No, Link Microtek Ltd will never share your data with any third-party.
6. Right of consent withdrawal
You may withdraw your consent for collecting your personal information at any time. To do so, please contact us at This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it..
7. Change or review of information
If you would like to review, change or delete personal data we have collected from you or you had submitted or permanently delete your account, please contact us.
For more information regarding the termination or deletion of your information, please refer to Section 9: Termination of this Privacy Policy.
8. Accessing or correcting your personal information
We take reasonable steps to accurately record the personal information that you provide to us, as well as any subsequent updates.
You have the right to ask for a copy of any of your personal data held by us.
We encourage you to review, update, and correct the personal information that we maintain about you. You may request that we delete personal data about you that is inaccurate, incomplete, and irrelevant for legitimate purposes, or is being processed in a way which infringes any applicable legal requirements.
Please contact our Data Protection Officer for more information on this process.
See section 15 below for contact details.
9. Termination of this Privacy Policy
You may at any time review or change the personal information we maintain about you by contacting Link Microtek Ltd. Upon your request, we will delete your contact information and personal data from our active databases.
This Privacy Policy is effective until terminated by either party. If you no longer agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy, you must cease the use of Link Microtek Ltd services. If you are dissatisfied with Link Microtek Ltd, or any of these terms, conditions, and policies, your sole legal remedy is to discontinue using the services. Link Microtek Ltd reserves the right to terminate or suspend your access to and use of the services without notice, if we believe, in our sole discretion that such use is in violation of any applicable law, or harmful to our interests or the interests of another person or entity, or where Link Microtek Ltd has reasons to believe that their use is in violation of this Privacy Policy.
10. Children’s Privacy
Link Microtek Ltd does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have personal information on a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information.
11. Changes to this policy
Link Microtek Ltd reserves the rights to change this Privacy Policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your use of the services after any such amendment or change in the Privacy Policy shall be deemed as your express acceptance to such amended/changed Privacy Policy and an assent to be bound by such changed/amended Privacy Policy. Information collected prior to the time any change is posted will be used according to the rules and laws that applied at the time the information was collected.
12. Governing law
This Privacy Policy and the use of the Website are governed by the laws of United Kingdom. The parties undertake to first try to resolve the dispute with by negotiation. If the parties fail to reach an amicable resolution through negotiation, Link Microtek Ltd agrees to submit the dispute to the competent Court of United Kingdom.
13. Copyrights
The copyrights of our Website are the property of Link Microtek Ltd.
Texts, graphics, photographs, animations, videos and clips, visible on the website are the object of copyright and are part of the intellectual property of Link Microtek Ltd. Those may not be reproduced, used, presented or represented without an explicit written permission by Link Microtek Ltd. Any distribution of files, obtained by the users of the website, or of parts of such files, constitutes a violation of the relevant intellectual property protection laws and is prosecuted by the law.
Nothing contained on this website may be interpreted as granting a license or right of use as a trademark without the prior explicit written consent of Link Microtek Ltd.
14. Miscellaneous
Link Microtek Ltd is controlled, operated and administered entirely within the United Kingdom.
If you are accessing the Link Microtek Ltd website from another jurisdiction, please be advised that you are transferring your personal information to Link Microtek Ltd in United Kingdom and, by using the website, you consent to that transfer and to abide by the applicable laws concerning your use of the website and your agreements with us.
This statement and the policies outlined in this Privacy Policy are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any third party.
15. Contacting us
If you have any questions about our website or this Privacy Policy or if you would like to request personal data that we may currently hold of yours, please contact our Data Protection Officer, Michelle Millet by telephone on +44 (0)1256 355771, by emailing This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it., or by post at Link Microtek Ltd, High Point, Church Street, Basingstoke, Hampshire, RG21 7QN.
Contact Us
Enquire today to find out more about our products and the service we offer.
Powered by ChronoForms - ChronoEngine.com
HomeAboutLink Microtek NewsLink Microtek Blog Archive NewsCompany PoliciesPrincipalsCase StudiesProductsDesignEMF SafetyIR CommsTest & MeasurementComponentsAmplifiers/Electron DevicesSatcomFeaturedRotary JointsNardalert S3Sunsight AAT-30 Antenna Alignment ToolRadMan 2LT & XT EMF Personal MonitorProduct SearchDesignComponentsRotary JointsSub-systemsProduct SearchEMF SafetyOur Products Personal MonitorsSurvey EquipmentArea Monitors & SoftwareProduct SupportCalibration & MaintenanceMeasurement ServicesApplication NotesTraining ServicesFAQsEMF NewsEMF BlogTrainingEMF Safety Course - RegistrationEMF Safety Tutorial - RegistrationOptical CommsAbout AzdecSystem OverviewApplicationsNavalAir Traffic ControlOther ApplicationsFAQsData SheetsLatest NewsTest & MeasurementNarda Test SolutionsSAFAWT GlobalSunsightContactCareers
